

PERSONAL INFORMATION

b.srihari10@gmail.com

Mobile (+91) 9000804057

Total work experience
6 Years 0 Month

KEY SKILLS

Responsive Web Design

Bootstrap

UI Development

User Interface Designing

Web Designing

Figma

Css/Css3

HTMI 5

Javascript And jQuery

OTHER PERSONAL DETAILS

City Hyderabad

Country INDIA

LANGUAGES

- English
- Telugu

Srihari Busarajula

UI UX Designe

PROFILE SUMMARY

M.tech(Computer science) is my Higher qualification (2016) and I have 6 years of experience as a UI / UX Designer and I have skill into HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 5, Javascript, Jquery and Figma, With the using of this technologies I am Designing static Responsive Web Pages into live Angular and React Projects and I did Mobile First Responsive Webpages

EDUCATION

2016 9 M.Tech

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU)

2013 P.Tech/B.E.

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU)

2009 **Y** XIIth

Telugu

2007 **Y** Xth

Telugu

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apr 2021 -Present **UI UX Designer**

Eclature Technologies

I am Working as a UI/UX Designer and I am using Figma tool. and also desinging static Responsive Webpages into live Angular and React Projects with Using Technologies (HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP 5, JAVASCRIPT AND jQuery)

Sep 2020 - Apr 2021 **UI** Developer

Cancri Techno solutions

web development with Html5, CSS3,Bootstrap4, javascript libraries, jQuery,Wordpress,psd to html Convert

Sep 2019 - Oct 2020

Web Developer

Sharpline Techno Solutions OR CA Techno Solutions

I have 1year experience with this Company and I am using HTML5, CSS 3, Bootstrap 4, Javascript, jQuery

May 2019 - Sep

2019

UI Developer

9Grid Technologies Private Limited

Projects

707 Days

TridaPro

TridaPro is Personalized 1-to-1 tutoring for students of all grades as well as Olympiad Preparation with Master Tutors

983 Days

Jupiter

Jupiter is web application which is used to store the data

0 Days

RiverZervs

Landing page created with Responsive design as per Requirement

0 Days

Payday

This Website is per Eclature company and it it for creating Payslips and salary details like this kind of things and this is for Payday 2.0 for Eclature

1317 Days

Hooter

It is a Angular Project and I am worked in Angular Components and This website is for reviewer website and My role creating web page with responsive as with the front end technologies Html5, Css3, Bootstrap5, jQuery, Slider like that

275 Days

Ebox

Mobile purchasing website and in i am worked on responsive design and i am worked on angular components

59 Days

Gluten-free Bakery

This site is a bakery site done with WordPress woocommerce theme which is name as VW BAKERY in this website everything is done by me like payments portal and shipping cart and delivery conditions and amount calculator and design done by me

61 Days

Topspotre

Topspotre is one the insurance company it provides lots services to customers

31 Days

Instaivy

this is online iot center designed by me

31 Days

Freshmindsoverseas

I AM Working developed a web site for consultancy services and the project name is freshminds.and the web site name is freshmindsoverseas.com with the WordPress Nasscom